# **Herwindo Artono**

<u>herwindo.artono@gmail.com</u> | +628122013050 | Jl. Cigadung Raya Barat No. 80A Bandung, Indonesia <u>Website | Github | Stackoverflow | Treehouse | freecodecamp | Portfolio</u>

## **PRODUCT MANAGER**

Product Manager with 2+ years experience building web and mobile application. Unique combined managerial and technical expertise with 3+ years experience in Front-end and Full-stack engineering and 5+ years in other management roles, this add a plus to lead many collaborations across teams while producing more precise strategy, roadmap and feature definition of a product.

#### **EXPERTISE:**

Product
 JIRA
 Kanban
 noSQL

Development • Confluence • Javascript • Node js

Strategic Planning
 Agile Methodology
 Vue
 Adobe XD

Marketing
 Scrum
 React
 Adobe Photoshop

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Front-end / Product Owner • 2017 - present

PT. T&E Simulation, Project Management Application

- In 3 months, launch a working attendance system to measure 32+ employees performance, that consist of web (SPA), mobile application, telegram bots, and AWS service.
- After product implementation, the team showed rough improvement in productivity by delivering a 12 month project in only 9 month (25% faster), the fastest project delivery in company.
- Operations Manager 2017 present

PT. T&E Simulation

- Managing resources to fulfill projects demands.
- Working with in house developer, building company's project management system application.
- Full Stack Engineer 2015 2017

PT. T&E Simulation, Wargaming Simulation Project

- Built 7 from total 26 Application (27%) to deliver in a year using Vue JS, socket.io, Node js, Express, Rethinkdb and Mongodb.

- Built 3 of 4 mobile application with API server in 3 month, this application intended to be installed in 50+ iPad using framework7, Vue, PWA, node is and socket.io.
- Lead front end engineering for a browser based application that serve prestigious training for national airforce. This Training held 4 to 5 times a year.
- Working in a team of 8 developers, Assisting the lead developer in standup meetings, git and kanban agile implementation.

### - Project Management Officer • 2012 - 2015

PT. T&E Simulation, various simulator project

- Supporting Project Managers, operating their projects.
- Setup Project management, Finance and Procurement system using Atlassian JIRA and Confluence, and also Trello, so that 3 projects with around 70+ employee have one single source of information they can access on site or at the office.
- Lead 20 person to do daily Test Dispatch Order for every day in 3 month on project's final product.
   Resulting a 3 years long project can be accepted by client in final crucial testing, Site Acceptance test.
- Documenting software & configuration versions.

### - **Project Manager** • 2010 - 2012

PT. T&E Simulation, Education Application Product

- Manage Team of 20 person to build Computer Based Training Application for National Wide Elementary and Junior High School
- The product delivered within 1 years, using Unity 3D

### **EDUCATION**

- Master of Business Administration • 2009 - 2012

Bandung Institute of Technology

Majoring in entrepreneurship, GPA: 3.45

- Bachelor of Economy • 2000 - 2005

Padjadjaran University

Majoring in Marketing Management, GPA: 3.04

#### NON FORMAL EDUCATION

Front-end and Full Stack Learning • 2018
 Freecodecamp

- Web App Development • 2015 - 2016

Envato Tutsplus Premium, codeschools, treehouse

# **LATEST CERTIFICATIONS & ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Completing 900 hours of freecodecamp represented coursework in roughly 320 hrs (2.8x faster)
  - Javascript Algorithms and Data Structure Certification 2018
  - API and Microservices Certification 2018
  - Responsive Web Design Certification 2018
- Winning design contest for banner ads 2018